5 Brown Ave, Roslindale, MA, 02131 ieloletin@gmail.com 419.360.2989

SUMMARY: I am a web developer, but I have also been an Aquarist and an EMT. Each experience along my career path has been about growth and change. With animals, exhibits, medicine and people, those alterations were ... As a web developer

Experience

General Assembly / Web Developer *in training*October 2016 - January 2017 | Boston, MA

Front End Application / Tic Tac Toe

Utilized HTML, SCSS, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript to create a front end tic tac toe project.

Full Stack Application / Read to Free

Utilized Ruby, Ruby on Rails, Handlebars, Bootstrap, HTML, SCSS, CSS and JavaScript to create a full stack personal library application.

Future Application / TBD

Will be updated upon project completion

Job Experience

Boston EMS / Emergency Medical Technician January 2014 - October 2016 | Boston, MA

Responded to emergency calls placed via the 9-1-1 system and interacted with the diverse population of Boston citizens in their homes, at work and outdoors, in all weather and sometimes hazardous environments. Assessed and treated patients according to local and state protocols as well as the standard operating procedures of Boston Emergency Medical Services. Administered medication and assisted paramedics with select medical treatments.

New England Aquarium / Aquarist

February 2010 - January 2014 | Boston, MA

Provided animal husbandry for marine and freshwater organisms through food preparation, feeding, cleaning, assisting with and administering medical treatments and recording observations of animal behavior. Maintained aquatic environmental parameters. Interviewed and hired seasonal interns. Supervised and trained volunteers and interns in animal handling, collection and husbandry.

Skills		
HTML	CSS	JavaScript
Ruby	SQL	Ruby on Rails
JQuery	Node	Handlebars
Express	Git	Bootstrap

Education

General Assembly 2016

Boston, MA
Web Developer Immersive

Northeastern University 2009

Boston, MA

Bachelors of Science: Biology

Additional Information

Portfolio: ariel-n-martin.com

GitHub: github.com/ielole

Interests

- Reading
- SCUBA diving
- Rock Climbing
- Black and White Photography
- Sustainable Energy
- Conservation